(Amy:)Look, I know you
don't like it,
(Amy:)but that's the point
of the experiment.
(Amy:)I need to irritate you
(Amy:)to find your optimal
anxiety zone.
(Amy:)And you said no to
tickling, polka music
(Amy:)or watching me
eat a banana.
(Sheldon:)Who eats them
horizontally?!
(Amy:)My mother said that's
how good girls do it.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps this was
a waste of time.
(Leonard:)Sheldon,
(Amy:)you're a remarkable scientist.
(Amy:)Just be patient-- I'm sure
you'll find the breakthrough
(Amy:)you've been looking for.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Amy:)And if you only
do solid research
(Amy:)instead of making
a groundbreaking discovery,
(Amy:)what does it matter?
"Only do solid research"?!
Uh... I come to you for help,
and you insult me?!
(Sheldon:)I thought the least that
you would do would be...
(Amy:)Look, your anxiety levels
are right in the zone.
(Sheldon:)Really?
(Sheldon:)Oh, that's fantastic.
N-Now, wait,
they're dropping.
(Sheldon:)Why are they dropping?
(Amy:)Because you're happy
they're elevated.
Oh, that is infuriating!
(Sheldon:)Ooh, look, they went
back up again.
(Sheldon:)Terrific.